Muhammad Ahsan Muneer

+923488300016

ahsanmuneer81@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ahsan-muneer/

in

https://portfolio-next-js-plum.vercel.app/

Senior Mobile and Web Application Developer with around 2+ years of experience in software development lifecycle (SDLC) including analysis, design, development, and testing, deployment, and documentation. Experience in Mobile Application Operating systems like iOS and Android. Skilled, motivated, and product-oriented mobile application developer with strong UI and UX design skills. Inquisitive and Highly-motivated software engineer, with strong web and mobile application skills. Forward-thinker by nature and loves to code

Skills

- React Native
- Reactis
- Nextjs
- JavaScript, ES6 and ES5

- Expo
- Github
- Firebase
- Google Map APIs

Experience

CURRENTLY WORKING

Software Engineer / Artistic Denim Mills MARCH 2021 - MARCH 2022

Senior Executive / Outsource in Pakistan

- Contribute to all phases of the development life cycle
- Develop and deploy new features to facilitate related procedures and tools if necessary
- Designing the application according to specifications
- Write well designed, testable, efficient code by using best software development practices
- Integrate data from various back-end services and databases

AUGUST 2020 - MARCH 2021

React Native Developer / Linkitsoft

Develop and Design Android IOS mobile apps. Creating web and mobile APIs in Asp.net, Integrating Payment Systems like Gkash and Stripe payment. Also Integrating Firebase Cloud Messaging FCM, Push Notifications, Third-Party APIs Integrating and Google map APIs.

Managing and Testing Mobile UI and UX.

Education

2016-2019

Bachelor in Software Engineering / Karachi University 2013-2015

Pre-Engineering / Jinnah College 2016-2018

Web and Mobile App Development Course / Saylani

Artificial Intelligence/ PIAIC